

O Barcelona, Spain

+34 640523319

Profile

I am a self-taught and independent DevOps Engineer with over three years of experience in developing applications, APIs, and innovative web solutions. My expertise extends to server development, Python, JavaScript, data analysis, and performance optimization. I excel in ensuring code maintainability and solving complex problems efficiently. My strong affinity for algebra amplifies my analytical and problem-solving abilities.

Employment History

DevOps enginier, Teleworking

April 2023 — November 2023

- Collaborated with a variety of clients to design, develop, and integrate tailor-made APIs into their ERP systems. (feel free to check out my projects for costumers on my GitHub).
- Managed and optimized server infrastructure, ensuring high availability, efficient performance, and secure operations for critical business applications. 2
- Recently focused on server operations, emphasizing performance enhancement and security enhancements, including OAuth2, encryption, over the past month.

Data analyst, Barcelona

January 2023 — March 2023

• I worked as a freelance helping people making web scraping to then covert to datasets, twitter bots, services etc. The main libraries I used were **Pandas**, **Numpy**, **Beautifulsoup**, etc.

Internship as a technician school, Barcelona

May 2021 — September 2021

 I worked helping people with little knowledge in computing and as a computer technician.

Education

DAM, Centre D'estudis Politèctic, Barcelona

September 2022 — Present

ES₀

September 2015 — July 2019

Escola Tecla Sala - Hospitalet Del Llobregat

SMIX, Escola joan pelegrí, Barclona

September 2019 — May 2022

Links

My own page

Github

Stronger skills

Python

Server manager

Fastapi

Linux

Javascript

Databases manager

Languages

Spanish

Catalan

English

Hobbies

1.2 personChees expertproblem solving